Everyone is a target.
Night of the Hunted is a horror, mystery, thriller
film directed by Franck Khalfoun.
When an unsuspecting woman stops at a remote gas station in the dead of night,
she's made the plaything of a sociopath sniper with a secret vendetta.
To survive, she must not only dodge his bullets and fight for her
life, but also figure out who wants her dead and why.
Alice, played by Camille Rowe.
Erik, played by Aleksandar Popovic.
Doug, played by J. John Bieler.
John, played by Jeremy Scippio.
Bob, played by Brian Breiter.
Cindy, played by Monaia Abdelrahim.
La nuit des traquées (English: The Night of the Hunted, lit.
The Night of the Stalking) is a 1980 French horror film directed and written by Jean
Rollin, and starring Brigitte Lahaie, Dominique Journet, and Catherine Greiner.
It follows a group of people who have lost their memories in an
environmental accident and are confined in a high-rise hospital.
The film explores themes of independent film, stalked by a
killer, convenience store, suspense thriller.
The tone is intense and dark and mind_bending.